>> Brian Holt: 转至 details.js，我们要这样做
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Go to details.js,
and we want to make it so
只要你点击这个好的按钮就可以打开一个模块
whenever you click on this nice button
here, that it pops open a module.
所以我们要做的就是进口
So what we're gonna do here
is we're going to import
从 @reach/router > > Brian Holt : And
navigate from @reach/router
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
我们也要进口我们的交通工具
we're going to import our modal as well.
模态的模态。
Modal from ./modal.
>> Brian Holt: 对不起， @reach，不反应， @reach/router。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Sorry, @reach,
not react, @reach/router.
>> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
我们会在这里添加一个新的国家，叫做 showModal 和
We'll add a new piece of state here,
and it's gonna be called showModal and
我们就不能开始了
we're not gonna initially show it.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，我们现在需要更多的动物状态。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, we need one
more piece of state from animal now.
我的意思是，它的 URL ，所以我要说 URL ，然后去把它从动物的 URL上拿掉。
I mean, its URL, so I'm gonna say URL and
get to grab that off of animal type URL.
这其实是你要去领养宠物的 URL 。
This is actually the URL that
you will go to to adopt the pet.
好的，在这里，我们将会推出一种新的方法，叫做肘式模式。
Okay, above the render here, we're going
to put a new method called toggle modal.
> > Brian Holt: 我们只做一个非常快捷的 showModal 的 this.setState ，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we'll just make this
a very quick this.setState of showModal,
你就想和任何一个
and you just want to be
the opposite of whatever
showModal 是， this.state.showModal。
showModal was, so this.state.showModal.
所以如果它是假的，让它成为事实，如果它是真的，就会使它成为错误。
So if it's false, make it true,
and if it's true, make it false.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then underneath that,
我们也要发挥作用了
we're gonna make an adopt
function as well.
这只是一支箭的功能
It's just gonna be an arrow function.
所有要做的都是导航到 this.state.url。
And all it's gonna do is
navigate to this.state.url.
>> Brian Holt: 我们也可以使用重定向组件完成此操作，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We could have done this
with the redirect component as well,
我想带你们两个
I wanted to show you both.
>> Brian Holt: 我不认为真的有优势。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I don't think
there is really an advantage.
React 路由器和 Reach 路由器人员鼓励您使用重定向
The React router and the Reach router
people encourage you to use a redirect
组件，这就是他们喜欢的内容。
component, that's what
they say they prefer.
但我认为这是一个非常好的决定
But I think it's a perfectly good
decision to decide either way.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，在这里，这里，在媒体里，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, down here,
here, inside of media,
我们要把 showModal 也放了我们要把它拿掉
we're gonna put showModal as well,
cuz we're gonna grab that out.
> > Brian Holt: 因此，我只在那里加上 41 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I just add 41 there.
>> Brian Holt: 在描述下，我们会把它放在这里。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then below
the description, we're gonna put this.
>> Brian Holt: 在此选择花括号，然后
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
pick up your curly braces here, and
然后我们要做一个三元的工作
then we're gonna do a ternary.
所以如果我要洗澡
So if I should showModal,
然后再显示这个
then display this,
抱歉莫代尔
I'm sorry, modal.
在这里面我们要把自己的标记
And inside of that,
we're going to put our own mark
是否 &lt;h1&gt; 要采用名称?
up of like &lt;h1&gt; Would
you like to adopt name?
>> Brian Holt: 然后将 div 和 className="按钮"放置。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then put a div and
className="buttons".
> > Brian Holt: 接下来，我们会说，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
then here, we're gonna say,
按钮 onClick= this.收养。
button onClick= this.adopt.
> > Brian Holt: 你会说，是的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And you say, yes.
然后你会说，不，我是个怪物，你只会把模型 toggle 。
And then you're gonna say, no, I'm
a monster, and you just toggle the model.
>> Brian Holt: 我的目标是让别人去买宠物。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: My goal is to
shame someone into buying a pet.
开个玩笑就买只宠物
Just kidding,
only buy a pet if you are ready for
一，但请收养所有宠物。
one, but please adopt all the pets.
> > Brian Holt: 接下来，在此括号后面，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then afterwards,
after this parenthesis right here,
我放了 :null，对吧 ?
I put :null, right?
因此，如果您告诉 " React " 可以根据您的猜测来呈现空值，那么它将不呈现任何内容。
So if you tell React to render null,
as you may guess, it renders nothing.
因此，如果您正在显示模态，那么将显示模态。
So if you're showing the modal,
then show the modal.
如果没有，那么显示模态，然后不显示任何内容。
If not, show modal then show nothing.
>> Brian Holt: 为什么不喜欢呢?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Why don't you like that?
>> Brian Holt: Fine，我是一个怪物。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Fine, I am a monster.
我不知道为什么会这样
I don't know why it's doing that.
然后我们要把它放在这里，当你点击这里的时候，在这个按钮上。
Then we have to put it so that when you
click on Adopt, here, on this button.
所以，在这里，你会说 " this.toggleModal " ，对吧 ?
So the onClick here,
you're gonna say this.toggleModal, right?
所以每当有人单击 " 采用 " 按钮时，它就会显示模态。
So whenever someone clicks on
the Adopt button, it shows the modal.
> > Brian Holt: 在这里，第 53 行，我添加的内容。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So line 53 here,
it's what I added.
我们去看看现在的情况。
Let's go take a look at
what looks like now.
所以我们在这里得到了最美好的孩子胖小子 Slim
So we got the goodest boy here,
Fat Boy Slim.
如果我点击胖子 Slim ，你愿意领养 Fatboy Slim吗 ?
If I click on Adopt Fat Boy Slim,
Would you like to adopt Fatboy Slim?
你说 " 是 " 或 " 否" 我是个怪物
And you say Yes or No, I'm a monster.
[ LAUGH] 所以如果你点击了 " 是 " ，它就会导航到
[LAUGH] So if you clicked yes,
it'll navigate to
胖男孩 Slim的 >> Brian Holt: 页面。
Fat Boy Slim's
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Page.
>> Brian Holt: 但如果您单击 " 否" ，我是一个怪兽，它会关闭模态。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But if you click on No,
I'm a monster, it closes the modal.
>> Brian Holt: 很酷，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Pretty cool, right?
只要重新调整我的想法就好了
So just to remphasize what
I think is cool about this,
此模态现在是 100% 的灵活性。
this modal is now 100% flexible.
任何时候我需要展示一个模态的时候，我就把它拉上来，就可以了。
Any time that I need to show a modal,
I just pull this in and it just works.
为了向你证明我的意思
And just to prove my point to you,
如果我在此处检查元素， >> Brian Holt: 通知
if I inspect element here,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Notice
我有模态和根这些是两个完全不同的地方
that I have modal and root, and
these are two totally different places.
但这一切都发生在根部外面，这真的很酷。
But this is all happening in here
outside of root, which is really cool.
但因为这就是 React ，就像我使用这个组件的功能一样，
But because this is on React, like I'm
using functions from this component,
我用的是作为成分出来的名字
I'm using the name,
which is coming out as components,
我在用它里面的所有东西但它却在另一个地方
I'm using all this stuff inside of it but
it's rendering somewhere else.
这真的很酷，因为如果你在做活动的听众，
It's actually really cool because
if you're doing event listeners, so
就说我有个关于 div 的事件听众在峰上
let's say I have an event listener
here on div, which is above the modal,
并单击 " onClick" 。
and say onClick.
它的所有内容都是 console.log 。
And all it does is console.log it.
> > Brian Holt: 现在，它还应该在这里工作，让我们确保我不会在这里发疯。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, it should still work
where, let's make sure I'm not crazy here.
>> Brian Holt: 好，因此单击侦听器正在工作。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
the click listener is working.
在我点击 div 的地方，它会展示这些事件。
Anywhere I click on the div,
it's gonna show these events.
但如果我点击这个，让我把这个垃圾给你看。
But if I click into this,
let me just trash this so you can see.
我在点击这个 div 之外的 DOM 元素
I'm clicking on DOM elements
outside of this div, but
它仍然被正确地分派了
it's still getting dispatched correctly.
因此，事件代表团实际上仍将经历相同的 React 树。
So the event delegation actually will
still go through the same React tree.
Cuz React 有自己的事件系统。
Cuz React has its own event system.
它看起来和它完全一样但它的特点是这样的
It looks exactly and it acts exactly the
same but it has nice features like this
我可以在那个 DOM 以外的地方处理事件代表团
where I can actually handle event
delegation outside of that DOM.
这也太酷了
That's really cool too.
我不知道为什么这应该有用，我只是对它着迷。
I don't know why this should be useful,
I'm just fascinated by it.
>> Brian Holt: Great，任何有关门户网站的问题 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Great,
any questions about portals?
这对像莫达斯这样的东西很有用，但也很有用
So this is useful for things like
modals but it also could be useful for
也许你又像个情境导航
like, maybe you have, again,
like a contextual navigation or
就像这样你可以用一个入口来处理
something like that,
you could handle that with a portal.
您可以处理特殊标题或
You could handle a special header or
一个特别的页脚或类似的东西
a special footer or
lots of things like that.
在 Netflix 上，我们使用入口向玩家渲染，因为玩家是
At Netflix, we used portals to render
into the player because the player was
另外还有一些很酷的东西你可以和他们一起做
a separate thing, so there's a bunch
of cool stuff you could do with them.
这曾经是不可能的
This used to be impossible,
用它来处理这些事情是不可能的
it used to be impossible to
handle these kinds of things.
实际上我们得用 Netflix 做这个疯狂的特殊的渲染
We actually had to build this crazy
special render that Netflix only used for
花了很长时间来处理这个问题
a long time to handle that.